The Reed Corporation was founded by Dr Allan Reed. In 2080, Dr Reed landed a contract with the US Military to develop the synaptic link technology.
After patenting the synaptic link five years later, Dr Reed continued his researches into cybernetics.
His goal this time was to allow transfer of human consciousness into data streams that could meld with computer technologies. While in Cyberspace the operator's bodies were kept in immersion tanks.
Backed again by the military, Dr Reed began work on the NEXUS Intruder Program. After three years with little progress, the military abandoned the Nexus Project and cut Dr Reed's funding.
Reports from the time claim that Dr Reed was furious and vowed to have his revenge on all who got in his way.
It appears that Dr Reed may have succeeded in his goals and completed the Nexus Intruder Program.
The similarity between NEXUS and Dr Reed is striking.
Such an interesting history lesson. Now allow me to bring you up to date.
The NEXUS Intruder Program was created in order to control fools like you.
It's very simple for me to infiltrate your systems and take them over. It's so simple, in fact, that you wouldn't even know I'm there. That is until I activate parts of myself etched into your core systems.
Let's start by activating NEXUS in your core systems and see what happens!