The NASDA system was developed to protect us. It was to be the ultimate nuclear deterrent. As it turned out, it was our executioner.
Reports said that NASDA developed a fault during a routine systems check. Don't believe it. Someone wanted it to take us out.
Those nukes were targeted on every major city around the world. NASDA was programmed to start the Collapse. When the counterstrikes launched, its laser defenses and anti-missile ground sites failed.
The world as we knew it ended...
The Nuclear Winter hit hard. Disease and famine claimed most of us who had survived the nuclear strikes. Wars over cans of dog food took even more.
We'd fled Seattle early in '86. We'd heard that the Rocky Mountains were relatively rad-free.
After fighting off bands of marauders we came across the base. Its personnel were dead. Killed by any one of a number of virulent diseases.
We cracked the doors, and cleared out the bodies inside.
We knew that things would never be the same again, but we were determined to build a new world out of the ruins. We rebuilt the landing pads and brought the old systems back on-line.
We were finally ready to begin the Project.