NASDA is the North American Strategic Defense Agency.
NASDA was formed in 2076 to defend North America from conventional and nuclear attack. The construction of a satellite defense system began in 2081 and was completed in 2082.
In 2085 the NASDA satellites fired their nukes at Earth.
There were also ground-based sites. Many of these were destroyed in the nuclear counterstrikes, but there's bound to be some out there.
The NASDA satellites also contained pulse-lasers designed to shoot down missiles approaching North America.
During the counterstrikes, these LasSats failed to fire. If brought into operation, these LasSats could inflict major damage on ground targets.
All nukes targeted at  North America found their targets.
We know that Nexus is searching for NASDA Central in the Eastern Sector. This was one of the land-based control centres for the satellites.
If the centre is found intact, NEXUS may gain control of the satellites.
Nexus claimed that it had already destroyed the world.