NASDA (PASKA) on Põhja Ameerika Strateegilise Kaitse Agentuur
NASDA loodi 2076. aastal, et kaitsta Põhja Ameerikat tava- ja tuumarünnakute eest. Satelliit kaitse süsteemide ehitamine algas 2081. ja lõppes 2082. aastal.
2085.aastal tulistasis NASDA satelliidid oma tuumapommidega Maad.
There were also ground-based sites. Many of these were destroyed in the nuclear counterstrikes, but there's bound to be some out there.
The NASDA satellites also contained pulse-lasers designed to shoot down missiles approaching North America.
During the counterstrikes, these LasSats failed to fire. If brought into operation, these LasSats could inflict major damage on ground targets.
Kõik tuumapommid, mis sihiti Põhja Ameerikasse tabasid märki.
We know that Nexus is searching for NASDA Central in the Eastern Sector. This was one of the land-based control centres for the satellites.
If the centre is found intact, NEXUS may gain control of the satellites.
Nexus claimed that it had already destroyed the world.